RG 163, Special Libraries Association, Connecticut Valley Chapter
Connecticut State Library
Special Libraries Association, Connecticut Valley Chapter records
1934-1987
Connecticut State Library
Special Libraries Association. Connecticut Valley Chapter
6.5 cubic feet
The Special Library Association was founded in 1909 in an attempt to bring together librarians whose jobs had actually created a new kind of librarianship, one geared to meet the needs of specialized situations. These records are from the Connecticut Valley Chapter.
RG163
Multiple
Historical Note
The Connecticut Valley Chapter of the Special Libraries Association officially formed on June 18, 1934. Previously special librarians from Connecticut met informally and at round table discussions at Connecticut Library Association meetings. In March of 1934 a group of eleven special librarians got together to discuss the possibility of forming their own chapter within the Special Libraries Association. After a meeting with the New York Chapter of the Special Libraries Association to discuss the benefits of an organized local chapter, the librarians decided to form their own chapter and held elections for officers in early June. A few weeks, the Special Libraries Association approved the affiliation of the Connecticut Valley Chapter.
In 1941, the Connecticut Valley Chapter hosted the Special Libraries Association Convention in Hartford. The Connecticut Valley Chapter also developed several union lists and bibliographies including lists of special collection in Connecticut and Massachusetts, a bibliography on the financial history of Connecticut and a union list of serials.
Scope and Content
The records include the constitution, by-laws, administrative files such as annual reports, minutes and lists of officers, newsletters, pamphlets, union lists, bibliographies, convention materials, information on projects undertaken by the chapter, legislation affecting librarians, photographs and memorabilia. The records consist of two different accessions which are labelled 1987-042 and 1988-007. In general these two accessions contain different information and records. However, there are some instances in which they overlap such as in the Administrative Files from the years 1945-1950. Such instances are noted in the finding aid.
Arrangement
Series 1: Constitution and By-Laws (1934 -1984) includes constitutions and by-laws of the organization and revisions made to the documents, duties of officers and committees, procedure manuals and a history of the chapter.
Series 2: Administrative Files (1934 -1987) includes minutes of the executive board and business meetings, annual reports, correspondence, lists of officers, committee chairpersons and members, and other information pertinent to each specific year.
Series 3: Publications (1934-1987) includes the Connecticut Valley Chapter's newsletter Bulletin and Special Library Association newsletters and pamphlets.
Series 4: Conventions and Conferences (1941-1978) includes information about the Special Libraries Association Convention in Hartford in 1941, the Special Libraries Association Convention in 1975 and the Governor's Conference on Library and Information Services.
Series 5: Projects (1965-1967, n.d.) includes information about an exhibit at the Bond Hotel in Hartford, the Seal Project to raise funds for the Connecticut Valley Chapter and a study undertaken by the education committee of the Special Libraries Association.
Series 6: Union Lists and Bibliographies (1949-1971) includes union lists and bibliographies developed by the Connecticut Valley Chapter. There is also correspondence regarding the Union List of Serials.
Series 7: Legislation (1945-1947) includes information about legislation impacting special librarians in Connecticut.
Series 8: News Clippings (1936-1942) includes news articles about the Connecticut Valley Chapter.
Series 9: Photographs (1940-1993) includes photographs of meetings.
Series 10: Memorabilia (1984) includes a paperweight from the 75th anniversary of the Special Libraries Association.
Related Material
None
Index Terms
Organizations:
Special Libraries Association.Connecticut Valley Chapter
Subjects:
Libraries--Connecticut River Valley--Records and correspondence; Special libraries--Connecticut River Valley--Records and correspondence
Places:
Connecticut River Valley
Occupations:
Librarians; Special Librarians
Document Types:
Administrative files; Clippings; Correspondence; Memorabilia; Photographs; Publications
Restrictions on Access
These records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Acquisition Information
The records were obtained from the Connecticut Valley Chapter of the Special Libraries Association.
Container List
- Series 1. Constitution and By-Laws, 1936-1983
  - 1987-042, 0.25 cubic feet (Box 1)
    - Constitution, 1936-1964 (Box 1)
    - Constitution, Revision of, 1936-1944 (Box 1)
    - By-Laws, 1953-1984, undated (Box 1)
    - Procedure manuals, 1947-1980 (Box 1)
    - Duties of officers, undated (Box 1)
    - History, 1934, undated (Box 1)
  - 1988-007, 0.25 cubic feet (Box 1)
    - Constitution, 1940 May-1964 March (Box 1)
    - Procedure manuals, 1941 November-1982 April (Box 1)
    - Duties of officers, 1980-1983 April (Box 1)
    - Duties of committees, 1982 June-1983 April, undated (Box 1)
    - History, 1945-1983 March (Box 1)
- Series 2. Administrative Files, 1934-1987
  - 1987-042, 2.0 cubic feet (Box 1)
    - 1945-1946, See also Accession 1988-007, Administrative Files, 1945-1946 (Box 1)
      - Minutes and reports: Executive Board, 1945 June-1946 June (Box 1)
      - Annual reports: Officers, 1946 (Box 1)
      - Annual reports: Committees, 1946 May (Box 1)
    - 1946-1947 (Box 1)
      See also Accession 1988-007, Administrative Files, 1946-1947
      - Minutes and reports: Executive Board, 1946 September-November (Box 1)
      - Minutes: Business meeting, 1946 July-1947 May (Box 1)
      - Annual reports: Officers, 1946 October-1947 May, undated (Box 1)
      - Correspondence: General, 1947 January-June (Box 1)
      - Correspondence: Vice President and Program Chairman, 1946 August -1947 May, undated (Box 1)
      - List of officers, 1946-1947 (Box 1)
      - List of members, 1946 July-August (Box 1)
    - 1947-1948 (Box 1)
      See also Accession 1988-007, Administrative Files, 1947-1948
      - Minutes and reports: Executive Board, 1947 July-December (Box 1)
      - Minutes: Business meeting, 1947 October-1948 April (Box 1)
      - Annual reports: Officers, 1948 May (Box 1)
      - Correspondence: General, 1947 June-1948 May, undated (Box 2)
      - Correspondence: Meetings, 1947 April-1948 June (Box 2)
      - President's newsletter, 1939-1947 (Box 2)
    - 1948-1949 (Box 2)
      See also Accession 1988-007, Administrative Files, 1948-1949
      - Minutes and reports: Executive Board, 1948 July-1949 April (Box 2)
      - Minutes: Business meeting, 1948 July-1949 April, undated (Box 2)
      - Annual reports: Officers, 1949 April-August (Box 2)
      - Annual reports: Committees, 1949 January-May (Box 2)
      - Correspondence, 1948 July-1949 June (Box 2)
      - Who's Who Directory, 1949 (Box 2)
      - Who's Who Directory: Forms, 1949 May-1950 April (Box 2)
      - Publicity Chairman correspondence, Press releases, and News clippings, 1948 August-1949 March (Box 3)
    - 1949-1950 (Box 3)
      See also Accession 1988-007, Administrative Files, 1949-1950
      - Annual reports: Officers, 1950 April-May (Box 3)
      - Annual reports: Committees, 1950 (Box 3)
      - Correspondence, 1949 October-1950 May (Box 3)
      - Meeting notices, 1949 October-1950 May (Box 3)
      - Newspaper, 1949 October (Box 3)
      - Special Library Association publications, 1949 May-1950 May, undated (Box 3)
    - 1950-1951 (Box 3)
      See also Accession 1988-007, Administrative Files, 1950-1951
      - Minutes: Business meeting, 1950 November-1951 April (Box 3)
      - Annual reports: Officers, 1951 May (Box 3)
      - Annual reports: Committees, 1951 Janurary-June (Box 3)
      - Correspondence, 1950 June-1951 July (Box 3)
      - Correspondence: Bulletin advertising, 1950 August-1951 May, undated (Box 3)
      - Meeting notices, 1950 August-1951 July (Box 3)
    - 1951-1952 (Box 3)
      - Minutes: Business meeting, 1952 March (Box 3)
      - Annual reports: Officers, 1952 April-May (Box 3)
      - Annual reports: Committees, 1952 April, undated (Box 3)
      - Correspondence, 1951 July-October (Box 3)
      - Correspondence: Bulletin advertising, 1951 November-December (Box 3)
      - List of members, 1951 Aug-1952 May (Box 3)
    - 1959-1960 (Box 3)
      - Correspondence, 1959 Decmeber (Box 3)
    - 1962-1963 (Box 4)
      See also Accession 1988-007, Administrative Files, 1962-1963
      - List of officers, 1962-1963 (Box 4)
      - Meeting notices, 1963 February (Box 4)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 4)
      See also Accession 1988-007, Administrative Files, 1963-1964
      - Annual reports: Officers, 1964 (Box 4)
      - Correspondence: Education Committee, 1962 September-1964 January, undated (Box 4)
      - List of officers, 1963-1964 (Box 4)
      - List of members, 1963-1964 (Box 4)
    - 1964-1965 (Box 4)
      See also Accession 1988-007, Administrative Files, 1964-1965
      - Minutes and reports: Executive Board, 1964 November (Box 4)
      - Annual Reports: Officers, 1965 (Box 4)
      - Annual Reports: Committees, 1965 April-June (Box 4)
      - Correspondence: General, 1964 October (Box 4)
      - Correspondence: Membership, 1964 November-1965 April (Box 4)
      - Correspondence: Sci-Tech Advisory Committee, 1964 July (Box 4)
      - List of officers, 1964-1965 (Box 4)
      - Governor's Committee on Libraries, 1961 May-1965 July (Box 4)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 4)
      See also Accession 1988-007, Administrative Files, 1965-1966
      - Minutes: Business meeting, 1965 August-1966 May (Box 4)
      - Annual Reports: Officers, 1966 (Box 4)
      - Annual Reports: Committees, 1966 (Box 4)
      - Correspondence, 1962 May-1966 July, undated (Box 4)
      - List of officers, 1965-1966 (Box 4)
      - Special Libraries Association President's Visit, 1962-1966 May (Box 4)
    - 1966-1967 (Box 4)
      See also Accession 1988-007, Administrative Files, 1966-1967
      - Annual Reports: Officers, 1966 July-1967 (Box 4)
      - Annual Reports: Committees, 1967 May (Box 4)
      - Correspondence: General, 1967 April (Box 4)
      - Correspondence: Membership, 1965 August-1967 May (Box 4)
      - List of officers, 1967 March-May (Box 4)
      - List of committee chairpersons, 1966 August (Box 4)
      - List of members, 1966 August (Box 4)
      - Recruitment materials, 1960-1967 (Box 4)
    - 1967-1968 (Box 4)
      See also Accession 1988-007, Administrative Files, 1967-1968
      - Minutes and reports: Executive Board, 1968 September-1969 May (Box 4)
      - Minutes: Business meeting, 1967 September-1968 May (Box 4)
      - Annual Reports: Officers, 1968 March-May (Box 4)
      - Annual Reports: Committees, 1967 June-1968 March (Box 4)
      - List of members, 1967-1968 (Box 4)
    - 1968-1969 (Box 4)
      See also Accession 1988-007, Administrative Files, 1968-1969
      - Minutes and reports: Executive Board, 1968 September-1969 May (Box 4)
      - Minutes: Business meeting, 1968 September-1969 May (Box 4)
      - Annual Reports: Officers, 1968-1969 (Box 4)
      - Correspondence, 1969 February (Box 4)
      - List of officers, 1969-1969 (Box 4)
      - List of committee chairpersons, 1968-1969 (Box 4)
      - List of members, 1969 (Box 4)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 5)
      See also Accession 1988-007, Administrative Files, 1969-1970
      - List of officers, 1969-1970 (Box 5)
      - List of committee chairpersons, 1969-1970 (Box 5)
      - List of members, 1969-1970 (Box 5)
      - Connecticut Valley and New York joint chapter meeting, 1970 (Box 5)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 5)
      See also Accession 1988-007, Administrative Files, 1970-1971
      - Minutes and reports: Executive Board, 1970 September-1971 February (Box 5)
      - Minutes: Business meeting, 1970 September-1971 Aprl (Box 5)
      - Correspondence: President, 1969 September-1971 May (Box 5)
      - List of members, 1970-1971 (Box 5)
      - Meeting notices, 1970 September-1971 January (Box 5)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 5)
      See also Accession 1988-007, Administrative Files, 1971-1972
      - Minutes and reports: Executive Board, 1971 July (Box 5)
      - List of officers, 1971-1972 (Box 5)
      - List of committee chairpersons, 1971-1972 (Box 5)
      - List of members, 1971-1972 (Box 5)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 5)
      See also Accession 1988-007, Administrative Files, 1972-1973
      - List of officers, 1972-1973 (Box 5)
      - List of committee chairpersons, 1972-1973 (Box 5)
      - Financial statement, 1972 May (Box 5)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 5)
      See also Accession 1988-007, Administrative Files, 1973-1974
      - List of officers, 1973 (Box 5)
      - List of committee chairpersons, 1973 (Box 5)
      - List of members, 1974 March (Box 5)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 5)
      See also Accession 1988-007, Administrative Files, 1974-1975
      - List of officers, 1974-1975 (Box 5)
      - List of committee chairpersons, 1974-1975 (Box 5)
      - List of members, 1975 July (Box 5)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 5)
      See also Accession 1988-007, Administrative Files, 1975-1976
      - Annual Reports: Officers, 1976 May (Box 5)
      - Annual Reports: Committees, 1975 May (Box 5)
      - List of officers, 1975 July (Box 5)
      - List of committee chairpersons, 1975 July (Box 5)
      - Meeting notices, 1976 (Box 5)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 5)
      See also Accession 1988-007, Administrative Files, 1976-1977
      - Annual Reports: Officers, 1976 December-1977 (Box 5)
      - Annual Reports: Committees, 1977 April-May (Box 5)
      - Correspondence: Corresponding Secretary, 1976 September-1977 May (Box 5)
      - Correspondence: Education Committee, 1976 October (Box 5)
      - List of officeres, 1976-1977 (Box 5)
      - List of committee chairpersons, 1976-1977 (Box 5)
      - List of members, 1976-1977 (Box 5)
      - Meeting notices, 1977 March-May (Box 5)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 5)
      See also Accession 1988-007, Administrative Files, 1977-1978
      - Annual Reports: Officers, 1978 July (Box 5)
      - Annual Reports: Committees, 1978 March-May (Box 5)
      - List of officers, 1977-1978 (Box 5)
      - List of committee chairpersons, 1977-1978 (Box 5)
      - List of members, 1977 (Box 5)
      - Meeting notices, 1977 September-1978 May (Box 5)
  - 1988-007, 2.0 cubic feet
    - 1934-1935 (Box 1)
      - Annual Reports: Officers, 1935 May (Box 1)
      - Correspondence, 1934 Dec (Box 1)
    - 1935-1936 (Box 1)
      - Annual Reports: Officers, 1936 May (Box 1)
    - 1936-1937 (Box 1)
      - Annual Reports: Officers, 1937 May-July (Box 1)
      - Correspondence, 1936 July-1937 July (Box 1)
    - 1937-1938 (Box 1)
      - Annual Reports: Officers, 1937 November-1938 May (Box 1)
      - Correspondence, 1938 January-March (Box 1)
      - List of members, 1938 (Box 1)
      - Meeting notices, 1937 October-1938 April (Box 1)
    - 1938-1939 (Box 1)
      - Annual Reports: Officers, 1938-1939 (Box 1)
      - Correspondence, 1938 July-1939 July\ (Box 1)
      - List of officers, 1938-1939 (Box 1)
      - Meetng notices, 1938 December-1939 April (Box 1)
      - Papers given at meetings, 1939 April (Box 1)
    - 1939-1940 (Box 1)
      - Annual Reports: Officers, 1939 November-1940 April (Box 1)
      - Annual Reports: Committees, 1940 May (Box 1)
      - Correspondence, 1939 November-1940 April (Box 1)
      - Meeting notices, 1940 April (Box 1)
    - 1940-1941 (Box 1)
      - Annual Reports: Officers, 1940 October-1941 May (Box 1)
      - List of members, 1941 January-February (Box 1)
    - 1941-1942 (Box 1)
      - Annual Reports: Officers, 1942 May (Box 1)
      - Annual Reports: Committees, 1942 May (Box 1)
      - Correspondence: General, 1941 November-1942 February (Box 1)
      - Correspondence: Program Committee, 1941 August-1942 May (Box 1)
      - List of members, 1941 December-1942 May (Box 1)
      - Meeting notices, 1942 March (Box 1)
      - Questionnaire, 1941 June-1942 Mach (Box 1)
    - 1942-1943 (Box 1)
      - Annual Reports: Officers, 1943 April-May (Box 1)
      - Annual Reports: Committees, 1943 May (Box 1)
      - Correspondence, 1942 July-1943 June (Box 1)
      - List of officers, 1942 (Box 1)
      - List of members, 1942 September-1943 May (Box 1)
      - Meeting notices, 1942 September-1943 June (Box 1)
    - 1943-1944 (Box 1)
      - Annual Reports: Officers, 1944 May (Box 1)
      - Annual Reports: Committees, 1944 May (Box 1)
      - Correspondence, 1943 October-1944 June (Box 1)
      - List of members, 1944 May (Box 1)
      - Meeting notices, 1943 Octoer-1944 May (Box 1)
    - 1944-1945 (Box 1)
      - Annual Reports: Committees, 1944-1945 (Box 1)
    - 1945-1946 (Box 1)
      See also Accession 1987-042 Administrative Files, 1945-1946
      - Minutes and Reports: Executive Board, 1945 July-1946 February (Box 1)
      - Minutes: Business meeting, 1946 January-July (Box 1)
      - Annual Reports: Officers, 1946 May (Box 1)
      - Annual Reports: Committees, 1946 May (Box 1)
      - Correspondence, 1945 September-1946 June (Box 1)
      - List of members, 1945 September (Box 1)
    - 1946-1947 (Box 2)
      See also Accession 1987-042 Administrative Files, 1946-1947
      - Annual Reports: Committees, 1947 May (Box 2)
      - Correspondence, 1946 May-1947 May (Box 2)
      - List of members, 1947 January (Box 2)
    - 1947-1948 (Box 2)
      See also Accession 1987-042 Administrative Files, 1947-1948
      - Annual Reports: Committees, 1948 May (Box 2)
      - Correspondence, 1947 September-1948 May (Box 2)
    - 1948-1949 (Box 2)
      See also Accession 1987-042 Administrative Files, 1948-1949
      - Annual Reports: Officers, 1949 May (Box 2)
      - Annual Reports: Committees, 1949 April-May (Box 2)
      - Correspondence, 1948 June-1949 May (Box 2)
      - Personnel records, 1949 January-April (Box 2)
    - 1949-1950 (Box 2)
      See also Accession 1987-042 Administrative Files, 1949-1950
      - Annual Reports: Committees, 1949-1950 (Box 2)
      - Correspondence, 1949 September-1950 June (Box 2)
    - 1950-1951 (Box 2)
      See also Accession 1987-042 Administrative Files, 1950-1951
      - Annual Reports: Committees, 1950-1951 (Box 2)
    - 1952-1953 (Box 2)
      - Meeting notices, 1953 February (Box 2)
    - 1962-1963 (Box 2)
      See also Accession 1987-042 Administrative Files, 1962-1963
      - Minutes and reports: Executive Board, 1962 June-1963 April (Box 2)
      - Minutes: Business meeting, 1962 September-1963 May (Box 2)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 2)
      See also Accession 1987-042 Administrative Files, 1963-1964
      - Minutes and reports: Executive Board, 1963 June-1964 June (Box 2)
      - Minutes: Business meeting, 1963 September-1964 May (Box 2)
      - Correspondence, 1963 July (Box 2)
      - list of members, 1963-1964 (Box 2)
    - 1964-1965 (Box 2)
      See also Accession 1987-042 Administrative Files, 1964-1965
      - Minutes and reports: Executive Board, 1964 July-1965 June (Box 2)
      - Minutes: Business meeting, 1964 September-1965 May (Box 2)
      - Correspondence, 1964 September (Box 2)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 2)
      See also Accession 1987-042 Administrative Files, 1965-1966
      - Minutes and reports: Executive Board, 1965 August-December (Box 2)
      - Minutes: Business meeting, 1965 September-1966 May (Box 2)
      - Annual Reports: Committees, 1966 February-April (Box 2)
    - 1966-1967 (Box 2)
      See also Accession 1987-042 Administrative Files, 1966-1967
      - Minutes and reports: Executive Board, 1967 January-June (Box 2)
      - Minutes: Business meeting, 1966 October-1967 May (Box 2)
    - 1967-1968 (Box 2)
      See also Accession 1987-042 Administrative Files, 1967-1968
      - Minutes and reports: Executive Board, 1967 October-1968 June (Box 2)
      - Minutes: Business meeting, 1967 September-1968 May (Box 2)
    - 1968-1969 (Box 2)
      See also Accession 1987-042 Administrative Files, 1968-1969
      - Minutes and reports: Executive Board, 1968 September-1969 June (Box 2)
      - Minutes: Business meeting, 1968 September-1969 May (Box 2)
      - Annual Reports: Officers, 1968-1969 (Box 2)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 2)
      See also Accession 1987-042 Administrative Files, 1969-1970
      - Minutes and reports: Executive Board, 1969 August-1970 March (Box 2)
      - Minutes: Business meeting, 1969 June-1970 May (Box 2)
      - Annual Reports: Officers, 1969-1970 (Box 2)
      - Annual Reports: Committees, 1970 March-April (Box 2)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 2)
      See also Accession 1987-042 Administrative Files, 1970-1971
      - Minutes and reports: Executive Board, 1970 June-1971 May (Box 2)
      - Minutes: Business meeting, 1970 September-1971 May (Box 2)
      - Annual Reports: Officers, 1971 May (Box 2)
      - Correspondence, 1970 December-1971 March (Box 2)
      - List of officers, 1970-1971 (Box 2)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 2)
      See also Accession 1987-042 Administrative Files, 1971-1972
      - Minutes and reports: Executive Board, 1971 July-1972 March (Box 2)
      - Minutes: Business meeting, 1971 October-1972 April (Box 2)
      - Annual Reports: Officers, 1971-1972 (Box 2)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 2)
      See also Accession 1987-042 Administrative Files, 1972-1973
      - Minutes and reports: Executive Board, 1973 February (Box 2)
      - Minutes: Business meeting, 1972 September-1973 May (Box 2)
      - Annual Reports: Officers, 1973 May (Box 2)
      - Meeting notices, 1973 (Box 2)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 2)
      See also Accession 1987-042 Administrative Files, 1973-1974
      - Minutes and reports: Executive Board, 1973 June-1974 April (Box 2)
      - Minutes: Business meeting, 1974 April (Box 2)
      - Annual Reports: Officers, 1973-1974 (Box 2)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 2)
      See also Accession 1987-042 Administrative Files, 1974-1975
      - Minutes and reports: Executive Board, 1974 September-1975 March (Box 2)
      - Minutes: Business meeting, 1974 September-1975 April (Box 2)
      - Annual Reports: Officers, 1974-1975 (Box 2)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 2)
      See also Accession 1987-042 Administrative Files, 1975-1976
      - Minutes and reports: Executive Board, 1975 October-November (Box 2)
      - Minutes: Business meeting, 1975 September-1976 May (Box 2)
      - Annual Reports: Officers, 1975-1976 (Box 2)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 2)
      See also Accession 1987-042 Administrative Files, 1976-1977
      - Minues and reports: Executive Board, 1976 September-1977 February (Box 2)
      - Minutes: Business Meeting, 1976 September-1877 May (Box 2)
      - Annual Reports: Officers, 1977 April (Box 2)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 2)
      See also Accession 1987-042 Administrative Files, 1977-1978
      - Minutes and reports: Executive Board, 1977 September-1978 May (Box 2)
      - Minues: Business meeting, 1977 August-1978 May (Box 2)
      - Annual Reports: Officers, 1978 July (Box 2)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 2)
      - Minutes and reports: Executive Board, 1978 September-1979 March (Box 2)
      - Minutes: Business meeting, 1978 September-1979 March (Box 2)
      - Annual Reports: Officers, 1979 April (Box 2)
      - Annual Reports: Committees, 1979 April (Box 2)
      - List of officers, 1979 March (Box 2)
      - List of committee chairpersons, 1979 March (Box 2)
      - List of members, 1978-1979 (Box 2)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 3)
      - Minutes and Reports: Executive Board, 1979-1980 May (Box 3)
      - Minutes: Business meeting, 1979 June-1980 May (Box 3)
      - Annual Reports: Officers, 1980 April (Box 3)
      - Annual Reports: Committees, 1980 March-April (Box 3)